It feels good.
気 持 ち いいんですね
You seem serious.
真面目そうですよね
Are you nervous?
緊張してますか?
I'm nervous.
緊張します
It's warm.
温かいですね
Is it warm?
温かいですか?
like?
好き?
I like it.
好きですよ
I feel like you're being proactive.
積極的な気がするんですね
After all, Jara's chikuri is about being eaten.
結局、ジャラのチクリはさ、食べてもらうっていうの
but.
が
How is it going?
どう なってますか?
It's getting really hard.
すごく硬くなってます
Is it getting hard?
硬くなってる?
Don't you hear about those parts?
そんなパーツは聞かないんですか?
Throw away the parts, parts.
パーツ捨ててね、パーツ
Shopping pin is out.
ショッピンピン出ちゃった
Do you want to see it?
見たいですか?
I want to see it.
見たいです
Well then,
じゃあ、
Take a good look at it for a day.
それ をよく見て一日
Take a good look one day.
よく見て一日
It's really big.
すごい大きいですね
May I?
いい ですか?
What about your dick?
チンポはどうですか?
It's really big.
すごい大きい
Look at me and say it's really big.
こっち見て、すごい大きいって言ってる
It's really big.
すごい大きいです
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいんですか?
Do you like big dicks?
大きいチンポは好き?
I like it.
好きです
好 きです
Do you like cock?
チンポ好き?
Just say it with your mouth.
ちょっと口だけでこいで
picture?
え?
Just use your mouth
口だけでこい
in.
で
Is something coming out?
何 か出てる?
is that so?
そうですか?
Shall we continue in bed?
続きはベッドでしましょうか
I won't let go of you.
チンチン離さないですね
sorry.
ごめんなさい
That's fine.
いいですよ